A Guide to the Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac Railroad Records, 1834-1997
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Finance Department, 1834-1995, 68.2 cubic feet and 371 volumes. (Box 64-255)
  - III.C. Securities 1834-1957
    - III.C.3. Dividends 1861-1957
      - Dividend Certificates Jan 1867-Jan 1899, 1 vol. (Box 121)
      - Dividends May 1880-Nov 1890, 1 vol. (Box 122)
      - Dividends 1891 Jan 1891-Jan 1898, 1 vol. (Box 122)
      - Dividends 1898 May 1898-Nov 1905, 1 vol. (Box 123)
      - Dividends Jan 1906-May 1914, 1 vol. (Box 123)
      - Ledger: Dividend Obligations and Scrip on Common Stock 1881, Dec 1881-Feb 1889, 1 vol. (Box 124)
      - Ledger: Dividend Obligations and Scrip in Guaranteed Stock 1884-1886, Apr 1886-Jul 1889, 1 vol. (Box 124)
      - Ledger: Dividend Obligations and Scrip on Common Stock 1894-1906, Jul 1889-Jul 1906, 1 vol. (Box 124)
      - Ledger: Dividend Obligations and Scrip in Guaranteed Stock Jan 1890-Jul 1906, 1 vol. (Box 124)
      - Ledger: Dividend Obligations and Common Stock Jul 1906-Feb 1916, 1 vol. (Box 125)
      - Dividends Obligations on Common Stock, Certificate No. 1 to No. 300 (Book No. 1) Jan 3 1882-Apr 1886, 1 vol. (Box 126)
      - Dividends Obligations on Common Stock, Certificate No. 301 to No. 601 (Book No. 2) Apr 1886-Aug 1887, 1 vol. (Box 126)
      - Dividend Obligations on Common Stock, Certificates, No. 600 to No. 899 (Book No. 3) Aug 1887-Nov 1889, 1 vol. (Box 127)
      - Dividend Obligations on Common Stock, Certificates, No. 900 to No. 1200 (Book No. 4) Nov 1889-Jan 1893, 1 vol. (Box 127)
      - Dividend Obligations on Common Stock, Certificate No. 1201 to No. 1700 (Book No. 5) Jan 1893-Mar 1901, 1 vol. (Box 128)
      - Dividend Obligations on Common Stock, Certificate No. 1701 to No. 2201 (Book No. 6) Mar 1901-Aug 1907, 1 vol. (Box 129)
      - Dividend Obligations on Common Stock, Certificate No. OA10001 to No. OA1250 Sep 1943-Jun 1949, 1 vol. (Box 130)
      - 25% Dividend Obligations on Common Stock, Certificate No. 1-100 3 Jan 1907, 1 vol. (Box 130)
      - 25% Dividend Obligations on Common Stock, Certificate No. 101-600 Jan 1907-Aug 1907, 1 vol. (Box 131)
      - Dividend Obligations on Guaranteed Stock, Certificate No. 154-417 (Book No. 2) Nov 1886-Jun 1887, 1 vol. (Box 132)
      - Dividend Obligations on Guaranteed Stock, Certificate No. 418-715 (Book No. 3) Jun 1887-Aug 1890, 1 vol. (Box 132)
      - Dividend Obligations on Gauranteed Stock, Certificate No. 716-1016 (Book No. 4) Aug 1890-Feb 1896, 1 vol. (Box 133)
      - Dividend Obligations on Guaranteed Stock, Certificate No. 1017-1317 (Book No. 5) 4 Mar 1896-Aug 1903, 1 vol. (Box 133)
      - Dividend Obliigations on Guaranteed Stock, Certificate No. 1318-1617 (Book No. 6) Aug 1903-Aug 1907, 1 vol. (Box 134)
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Certificate No. 1-500 Dec 1907-Mar 1910, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Fractional, Certificate No. 1001-1500 Feb 1916-Jan 1917, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Certificate No. 2001-2500 Dec 1922-May 1923, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Certificate No. 2501-3000 May 1923-Jan 1925, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Certificate No. 3001-3500 Jan 1925-Aug 1929, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Certificate No. 3501-4000 Aug 1929-Apr 1934, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Fractional, Certificate No. 4001-4250 Apr 1934-Aug 1936, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Fractional, Certificate No. 4251-4500 Aug 1936-Mar 1939, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Fractional, Certificate No. 4501-4750 Mar 1939-Feb 1940, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Fractional, Certificate No. 4751-5000 Feb 1940-Jul 1941, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Fractional, Certificate No. 5001-5250 Jul 1941-May 1942, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Fractional, Certificate No. 5251-5500 May 1942-Mar 1943, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Fractional, Certificate No. 5501-5750 Mar 1943-Dec 1943, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Fractional, Certificate No. 5751-6000 Dec 1943-Mar 1945, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Fractional, Certificate No. 6001-6250 Mar 1945-Jan 1946, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Fractional, Certificate No. 6251-6500 Feb 1946-Dec 1946, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Fractional, Certificate No. 6501-6750 Dec 1946-Jan 1948, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Fractional, Certificate No. 6751-700 Jan 1948-Apr 1949, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Fractional, Certificate No. 7001-7250 Apr 1949-Jun 1949, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations (less than $10,000), Fractional, Certificate No. 7251-7500, none issued, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations, $10,000, Certificate No. A1-A500, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Obligations, $10,000, Certificate No. A501-A1000, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Record 2 Nov 1914-31 Dec 1921, 1 vol. (Box 135)
      - Dividend Record 1 May 1922-31 Dec 1924, 1 vol. (Box 135)
      - Dividend Record 1947-1949, 1 vol. (Box 136)
      - Dividend Record 1950-1951, 1 vol. (Box 136)
      - Dividend Record 1952, 1 vol. (Box 136)
      - Dividend Record 1953, 1 vol. (Box 137)
      - Dividend Record 1954, 1 vol. (Box 137)
      - Dividend Record 1955, 1 vol. (Box 137)
      - Dividend Record 1956, 1 vol. (Box 138)
      - Dividend Record 1957, 1 vol. (Box 138)
      - Dividend Scrip, Convertible Jan 1882-Jan 1887, 1 vol. (Box 139)
      - Dividend Scrip, Certificate No. 1-252 Jan 1907-Apr 1907, 1 vol. (Box 140)
      - Dividend Scrip, Certificate No. S1-S500 Feb 1916-Jul 1916, 1 vol. (Box 141)
      - Dividend Warrants, $1000, Due 1881 1870, 1 vol. (Box 141)
      - Transfer Book, Dividend Certificates Apr 1869-Mar 1899, 1 vol. (Box 142)
      - Dividend Obligation Transfer Book Jan 1882-Feb 1887, 1 vol. (Box 143)
      - Dividend Obligation Transfer Book Feb 1887-Aug 1890, 1 vol. (Box 143)
      - Dividend Obligation Transfer Book Apr 1890-Apr 1896, 1 vol. (Box 143)
      - Dividend Obligation Transfer Book Apr 1896-Jan 1904, 1 vol. (Box 144)
      - Dividend Obligation Transfer Book Jan 1904-Dec 1910, 1 vol. (Box 144)
      - Dividend Obligation Transfer Book Jan 1911-Feb 1916, 1 vol. (Box 145)
    - III.C.4. Stocks 1834-1975
      - Certificates of Stock, No. 396-770 1837-Sep 1850, 1 vol. (Box 146)
      - Certificates of Common Stock, No. 925-1528 Jan 1867-Nov 1871, 1 vol. (Box 146)
      - Certificates of Stock, No. 1529-2017 Dec 1871-Mar 1887, 1 vol. (Box 146)
      - Certificates of Common Stock, No. 1152-1415 Mar 1855-Feb 1866, 1 vol. (Box 147)
        Includes: renewal for lost Certificates No. 928-951
      - Certificates of Common Stock, No. 2018-2408 Jun 1887-Jun 1907, 1 vol. (Box 147)
      - Certificates of Common Stock, Less than 100, C1-C500 Sep 1907-Apr 1949, 1 vol.
      - Certificates of Common Stock, 100 Shares, CA1-CA500 Sep 1907-Dec 1918, 1 vol.
      - 6% Guaranteed Stock 1866, Certificate No. 1-230 1 Jan 1867-Mar 1916, 1 vol. (Box 148)
      - 6% Guaranteed Stock 1871, Certificates, GD1-GD250 Apr 1916-Apr 1949, 1 vol. (Box 149)
      - 6% Non-voting Stock, Certificates, Issued to New York Trust Co., 1920; transferred to Richmond-Washington Co., 1941, 1 vol. (Box 150)
        Includes: papers relating to the redemption of shares 1941
      - 6% Non-voting Stock, Certificates, Issued to the Richmond-Washington Co., June 1941, 1 vol. (Box 150)
        Includes: papers relating to the redemption of shares, Apr 1947
      - 7% Guaranteed Stock 1866, Certificates No. 1-235 Jan 1867-Aug 1882, 1 vol. (Box 150)
      - 7% Guaranteed Stock 1968, Certificates No. 1-228 Jan 1869-Aug 1888, 1 vol. (Box 150)
      - 7% Guaranteed Stock 1868, Certificate No. 237 Apr 1889, 1 vol. (Box 150)
      - 7% Guaranteed Stock 1866, Certificates No. 236-464 Aug 1882-Apr 1907, 1 vol. (Box 151)
      - 7% Guaranteed Stock 1871, Certificates No. 1-27 Jun 1875-Oct 1916, 1 vol. (Box 152)
      - 7% Guaranteed Stock 1871, Certificates No. DE1-200 Aug 1921-Aug 1948, 1 vol. (Box 153)
      - 7% Guaranteed Stock 1871, Certificates, G501-750 Aug 1948-Jun 1949, 1 vol. (Box 153)
      - Guaranteed Stock, Certificate No. 1-353 May 1857-May 1907, 1 vol. (Box 154)
      - Guaranteed Stock, Certificates, 100 Shares GA1-100 Nov 1907-Oct 1945, 1 vol. (Box 155)
      - Guaranteed Stock, Less than 100, Certificates G1-G300 Sep 1907-Feb 1935, 1 vol. (Box 156)
      - Guaranteed Stock, Less than 100, Certificates G301-G500 Feb 1935-Aug 1948, 1 vol. (Box 157)
      - Guaranteed Stock, Less than 100, Certificates G501-G750 Mar 1939-Jun 1949, 1 vol. (Box 157)
      - Guaranteed Stock, Less than 100, Certificates GB 100-500 Sep 1907-Mar 1939, 1 vol.
      - Stock Ledger A, Stockholders of the Richmond, Fredericksburg and Potomac Railroad Company 1835-1852, 1 vol. (Box 158)
        Stockholders are listed alphabetically with place of residence
      - Stock Ledger B, New Stock, payment by Installment 1834, 1837-1852, 1 vol. (Box 158)
      - Stock Ledger in four volumes: A-D; E-L; Mc-SA; SI-Z 1907-1948, 4 vols. (Box 159-162)
      - Stock Ledger, Common Stock 1852-1906, 1 vol. (Box 163)
      - Ledger, 6% Guaranteed Stock 1867-1887, 1 vol. (Box 164)
      - Ledger, 7% Guaranteed Stock 1866, 1868, 1867-1881, 1 vol. (Box 164)
      - Ledger, Guaranteed Stock May 1881-Jul 1906, 1 vol.
      - Ledger, Guaranteed Stock Jul 1906-Feb 1916, 1 vol. (Box 165)
      - Index to Unidentified Stock Ledger n.d., 1 vol. (Box 165)
      - Transfer Book, Capital Stock Jan 1835-Apr 1850, 1 vol. (Box 166)
      - Transfer Book, Capital Stock Apr 1850-Jun 1859, 1 vol. (Box 167)
      - Transfer Book, Capital Stock Aug 1859-May 1885, 1 vol. (Box 167)
      - Transfers, Guaranteed Stock Jun 1859-Mar 1916, 1 vol. (Box 168)
      - Transfer Book, 7% Guaranteed Stock Mar 1867-Aug 1880, 1 vol. (Box 168)
      - Transfer Book, 6% Guaranteed Stock Apr 1867-Oct 1888, 1 vol. (Box 168)
      - Transfers, Common Stock May 1859-Mar 1916, 1 vol.
      - Stock Transfer Register 1945-1950, 1 vol.
      - Stock Transfer Register 1951-1955, 1 vol.
      - Stock Transfer Register 1956-1960, 1 vol.
      - Stock Transfer Register 1961-1964, 1 vol.
      - Stock Transfer Register 1965-1972, 1 vol.
      - Stock Transfer Register 1973-1975, 1 vol.
    - III.C.5 Mixed Volumes 1867-1945
      - Interest on Registered Bonds and Certificates of Debt 1880-1902, 1 vol.
      - Dividend Certificates, 6% Bonds Due 1880[7], and 8% Coupon Bonds 1867-1886, 1 vol. (Box 169)
      - Registered Bonds and Certificates [of Debt] Ledger Jan 1886-Mar 1902, 1 vol. (Box 169)
      - Transfer Record [Guaranteed Stock, Common Stock, Dividend Obligations] Feb 1916-Jan 1932, 1 vol.
      - Transfer Record [Guaranteed Stock, Common Stock, Dividend Obligations] Jan 1932-Jun 1945, 1 vol.
    - III.C.6. Securities - Cancelled 1880-1902
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 13 Jan 1879-1 Jun 1880 (Box-folder 170:1-10)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 7 Jun 1880-14 Oct 1881 (Box-folder 171:1-9)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 14 Oct 1881-14 Jul 1882 (Box-folder 172:1-8)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 17 Jul 1882-2 Jun 1883 (Box-folder 173:1-6)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 9 Jun 1883-3 Apr 1884 (Box-folder 174:1-7)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 5 Apr 1884-26 Sep 1885 (Box-folder 175:1-9)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 26 Sep 1885-27 Apr 1886 (Box-folder 176:1-7)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 28 May 1886-20 Nov 1886 (Box-folder 177:1-7)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 22 Nov 1886-26 Feb 1889 (Box-folder 178:1-8)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 1 Mar 1889-11 Feb 1890 (Box-folder 179:1-9)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 12 Feb 1890-19 Feb 1892 (Box-folder 180:1-9)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 19 Feb 1892-Mar 1893 (Box-folder 181:1-9)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 16 Mar 1893-4 Apr 1894 (Box-folder 182:1-8)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 27 Apr 1894-16 Mar 1895 (Box-folder 183:1-8)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 22 Mar 1895-12 Jun 1896 (Box-folder 184:1-8)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 10 Jul 1896-12 Aug 1897 (Box-folder 185:1-8)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 10 Aug 1897-15 Dec 1898 (Box-folder 186:1-8)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 13 Mar 1899-4 Nov 1899 (Box-folder 187:1-9)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 13 Nov 1899-12 Mar 1900 (Box-folder 188:1-9)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 10 Mar 1900-14 Jun 1900 (Box-folder 189:1-9)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 15 Jun 1900-4 Apr 1901 (Box-folder 190:1-12)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 10 Apr 1901-11 Mar 1902 (Box-folder 191:1-11)
      - Cancelled Stock Certificates 12 Mar 1902-13 Mar 1902 (Box-folder 192:1-7)
    - III.C.7. Securities - Miscellaneous Files 1878-1901
      - Bonds Paid 1901 (Box-folder 193:1-8)
      - Orders to pay 1878-1881, 1882 (Box-folder 193:9)
      - Powers of Attorney 1880-1882 (Box-folder 193:10)
  - III.D. Tax Records 1914-1992
    Includes: 1. Federal Tax Reports and Returns 2. State Tax Reports and Returns 3. Property/Real Estate Tax 4. Misc. Tax Subject Files
    If not mentioned otherwise, arranged by tax year
    - III.D.1. Federal Tax - Reports and Returns 1916-1968
      - III.D.1.1. Agent's Reports for 1918-1929
        - Tax years 1918-1922, 1925-1926; Settlement basis (1931) (Box-folder 194:1)
        - Tax Year 1920; Surplus Wash. South. Merger (Box-folder 194:2)
        - Tax years 1920-1922, 2 Aug 1926 (Box-folder 194:3)
        - Tax years 1920-1922, 29 Jan 1927 (Box-folder 194:4)
        - Tax years 1920-1922 returns (Adjustments of net-income) (Box-folder 194:5)
        - Tax years 1920-1922; Final settlement (Box-folder 194:6)
        - Tax years 1923-1925, 6 Jun 1927 (Box-folder 194:7)
        - Tax years 1923-1925, 21 Jan 1928 (Box-folder 194:8)
        - Tax years 1923-1925; Returns (Adjustment of net-income) (Box-folder 194:9)
        - Tax year 1924, 12 Mar 1930 (Box-folder 194:10)
        - Tax year 1924, Refund, 1930 (Box-folder 194:11)
        - Tax year 1925, Refund, 1933 (Box-folder 194:12)
        - Tax years 1925-1926, 12 May 1929 (Box-folder 194:13)
        - Tax year 1926, 24 Nov 1928 (Box-folder 194:14)
        - Tax years 1926-1928; Returns (Box-folder 194:15)
        - Tax years 1927-1928, 1 Feb 1930 (Box-folder 194:16)
        - Tax years 1927-1928, 6 Jun 1930 (Box-folder 194:17)
        - Tax year 1928; Refund 1933 (Box-folder 194:18)
        - Tax year 1929, 20 Feb 1931 (Box-folder 194:19)
        - Tax year 1929, 3 Jan 1932 (Box-folder 194:20)
        - Tax year 1929, 19 Jul 1932 (Box-folder 194:21)
        - Tax year 1929, 21 Oct 1932 (Box-folder 194:22)
        - Tax year 1929; U.S.B.T.A. 8 Feb 1936 (Box-folder 194:23)
        - Tax years 1920-1929; Index to income and returns (Box-folder 194:24)
      - III.D.1.2. Federal Income Tax Returns by Tax Year 1916-1968
        Income Tax Returns include for the most part copies of returns, instructions, schedules, income statements, worksheets, receipts, correspondence, balance sheets, etc.
        Arrangement follows original order: folders were kept generally by year; in cases parts of the annual return file had separate folder titles; those were kept as well.
        - Federal Income Tax, Tax year 1916 (Box-folder 195:1-3)
        - Federal Income Tax, Tax year 1917 (Box-folder 195:4-7)
        - Federal Income Tax, Tax years 1917-1925 (Box-folder 196:1)
        - Federal Income Tax, Tax year 1918 (Box-folder 196:2-6)
        - Federal Income Tax, Tax year 1918, Worksheets (Box-folder 197:1-4)
        - Federal Income Tax, Tax years 1918-1922 (Box-folder 197:5)
        - Federal Income Tax, Yax year 1919 (Box-folder 198:1-4)
        - Federal Income Tax, Tax year 1919, Worksheets (Box-folder 199:1-5)
        - Federal Income Tax, Tax year 1920 (Box-folder 200:1-3)
        - Federal Income Tax, Tax year 1920, Worksheets (Box-folder 200:1-2)
        - Federal Income Tax, Tax year 1920-1922, Appeals (Box-folder 201:1-5)
        - Federal Income Tax, Tax year 1920-1922, Refund suits (Box-folder 201:6-8)
        - Federal Income Tax, Tax year 1921 (Box-folder 202:1-3)
        - Federal Income Tax, Tax years 1921-1926, Consolidation of returns (Box-folder 202:4)
        - Federal Income Tax, Tax year 1922 (Box-folder 202:5-7)
        - Federal Income Tax, Tax year 1923 (Box-folder 203:1)
        - Federal Income Tax, Tax year 1924 (Box-folder 203:2-5)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1925 (Box-folder 203:6-8)
          Includes petition to U.S.B.T.A.(1929)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1926 (Box-folder 204:1-3)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1927 (Box-folder 204:4-5)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1928 (Box-folder 204:6)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1929 (Box-folder 205:1-3)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1929, Retirements, 2 folders (Box-folder 205:4-5)
          Includes petitions to U.S.B.T.A.
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1929, Discount (Box-folder 206:1)
          Includes draft of petition to U.S.B.T.A.
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1929, Guaranteed stock (Box-folder 206:2-3)
          Includes petition to U.S.B.T.A.
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1929, Opinion - U.S.B.T.A. (Box-folder 206:4-6)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1930 (Box-folder 207:1-6)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1931 (Box-folder 208:1-2)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1932 (Box-folder 208:3)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1933 (Box-folder 208:4-5)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1934 (Box-folder 208:6)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1935 (Box-folder 208:7-8)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1936 (Box-folder 209:1)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1937 (Box-folder 209:2)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1938 (Box-folder 209:3)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1939 (Box-folder 209:4)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1940 (Box-folder 209:5-6)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1941 (Box-folder 210:1-3)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1942 (Box-folder 210:4-7)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1943 (Box-folder 211:1-4)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1944 (Box-folder 212:1-5)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1945 (Box-folder 212:6-10)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1946 (Box-folder 213:1-3)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1947 (Box-folder 213:4-6)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1948 (Box-folder 214:1-3)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1949 (Box-folder 214:4-7)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1950 (Box-folder 215:1-5)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1951 (Box-folder 216:1-4)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1952 (Box-folder 216:5-8)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1952 [1941-1950 Vacation plan accrual] (Box-folder 217:1-3)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1953 (Box-folder 217:4-6)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1954 (Box-folder 218:1-7)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1954, Retirements (Box-folder 218:8-13)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1955 (Box-folder 219:1-5)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1955, Retirements (Box-folder 219:6-7)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1956 (Box-folder 219:8-14)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1956, Retirements (Box-folder 220:1)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1957 (Box-folder 220:2-6)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1957, Retirements (Box-folder 220:7-9)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1958 (Box-folder 221:1-7)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1958, Retirements (Box-folder 221:8)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1959 (Box-folder 222:1-7)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1959, Retirements (Box-folder 222:8)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1960 (Box-folder 223:1-9)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1960, Retirements (Box-folder 223:10)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1961 (Box-folder 224:1-8)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1961, Retirements (Box-folder 224:9)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1962 (Box-folder 225:1-9)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1962, abnormal retirements (Box-folder 225:10)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1962, Retirements (Box-folder 225:11)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1963 (Box-folder 226:1-9)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1963, Abnormal retirements (Box-folder 226:10-11)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1963, Retirements (Box-folder 227:1)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1964 (Box-folder 227:2-7)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1964, Retirements (Box-folder 227:8-9)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1965 (Box-folder 228:1-8)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1965, Retirements (Box-folder 228:9-11)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1966 (Box-folder 229:1-4)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1966, Retirements (Box-folder 229:5-8)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1967 (Box-folder 230:1-4)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1967, Retirements (Box-folder 230:5-9)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1968 (Box-folder 231:1-4)
        - Federal Income tax, Tax year 1968, Retirements (Box-folder 231:5-8)
    - III.D.2. State Tax Reports, Tax Returns, and Rolling Stock Information, 1933-1991
      - III.D.2.1. Annual Tax Reports of Railroad Companies - Report of the R.F. & P. to the Dept. of Taxation of Virginia 1985-1991
        - Tax years 1985-1987 (Box-folder 232:1)
        - Tax years 1988-1989, 2 copies each (Box-folder 232:2)
        - Tax year 1990, 3 copies (Box-folder 232:3)
        - Tax year 1991 (Box-folder 232:4)
      - III.D.2.2. Virginia State Tax Returns 1933-1961
        State Tax returns and Rolling Stock Information include 1 or 2 copies of returns, schedules, and in some cases statement of property value and taxes extended made by the State Corporation Commission of Virginia.
        - State Tax Return 1933 (Box-folder 233:1-3)
        - State Tax Return 1934 (Box-folder 233:4-5)
        - State Tax Return 1940 (Box-folder 234:1-3)
        - State Tax Return 1941 (Box-folder 234:4-5)
        - State Tax Return 1942 (Box-folder 235:1-3)
        - State Tax Return 1943 (Box-folder 235:4-5)
        - State Tax Return 1944 (Box-folder 236:1-2)
        - State Tax Return 1945 (Box-folder 236:3-4)
        - State Tax Return 1946 (Box-folder 237:1-2)
        - State Tax Return 1947 (Box-folder 237:3-4)
        - State Tax Return 1948 (Box-folder 238:1-2)
        - State Tax Return 1949 (Box-folder 238:3-4)
        - State Tax Return 1950 (Box-folder 238:5-6)
        - State Tax Return 1951 (Box-folder 239:1-3)
        - State Tax Return 1952 (Box-folder 239:4-5)
        - State Tax Return 1954 (Box-folder 240:1-2)
        - State Tax Return 1954 (Box-folder 240:3-5)
        - State Tax Return 1955 (Box-folder 241:1-2)
        - State Tax Return 1956 (Box-folder 241:3-4)
        - State Tax Return 1957 (Box-folder 241:5-6)
      - III.D.2.3. State Tax Return Rolling Stock Information (Class 5 Schedules)
        - Rolling Stock Information 1928-1929 (Box-folder 242:1)
        - Rolling Stock Information 1930-1931 (Box-folder 242:2)
        - Rolling Stock Information 1932-1933 (Box-folder 242:3)
        - Rolling Stock Information 1934-1935 (Box-folder 242:4)
        - Taxes on Rolling stock 1934-1942, 2 folders (Box-folder 242:5-6)
        - Rolling Stock Information 1936-1937 (Box-folder 242:7)
        - Rolling Stock Information 1938-1939 (Box-folder 243:1)
        - Rolling Stock Information 1940-1941 (Box-folder 243:2)
        - Rolling Stock Information 1942 (Box-folder 243:3)